megainformationtech.com 2015-06-01

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Statement

Mega Information Technology Limited Corp. is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our offerings. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. This Privacy Statement only covers the site Mega.

## Aggregated Information

Aggregated information, such as which page users access or visit and information volunteered by users, is collected through various methods. For example, Mega collects IP addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web. Web servers (the computers that "serve up" web pages) automatically identify your computer by its IP address, and when you request a page from Mega, our servers log your IP address. Mega only uses IP addresses for the purposes of web traffic analysis and trends.

## Use of Cookies

Mega also uses cookies to store information. A cookie is a small data file that most major web sites write to your hard drive for record keeping purposes when you visit them. Cookies allow Mega to measure activity on the site and to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences.

## Children and Privacy

Mega encourages parents and guardians to spend time with their children online, and to be fully familiar with the sites visited by their children.  
Individuals under 13  
No information should be submitted to or posted on Mega by users under the age of 13 years without the consent of their parent or guardian. Mega does not provide any personally identifying information for users under the age of 13, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever unless disclosed during collection.

## Links to Other Sites

It is important to note that Mega contains links to sites other than Mega and that those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as Mega. 

## Effect of Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party. Mega reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time and users will be notified of any changes made.

USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR CONSENT TO THIS ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE.
